I want to show my gym.
>> Let's go to the gym first.
>> Yeah,
>> I can keep this.
>> No, no, no. Give it to her,
>> brother. Touch my money again. We're
going to have to wrestle.
>> No. Give it to her. You're not stupid.
Give it to her.
>> She makes a lot of money. The UFC pays
her.
>> How you know?
>> Cuz she told me.
>> No. No. It's not good.
>> Take it to her. Nina. Nina. Take it.
Take it. Don't. Don't. Take. Ow.
Where's your gym, bro? Let's just see
how rich you are. Let's go.
>> Yo,
it's up.
>> GIVE ME YOUR GUN. STOP. GIVE ME A GUN.
>> GIVE ME YOUR GUN.
Are
>> you [__] kidding me,
>> brother? Now come here.
>> I knew it. That's why I didn't want to
stand next. I knew it.
>> Yo, stop running, bro.
Are you [__] kidding me?
>> It's okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my god.
>> You're lucky I threw my phone, bro. I
would have had to kill you. Shangle you
to death,
>> brother. I wouldn't I'm stealing I'm
stealing your [__] dog. I'm stealing
your dog.
Can't even [__] get in.
>> After everything we
>> What were you thinking?
Get my phone, bro.
>> I'm about to crash out. I threw it.
>> I threw it somewhere, bro. I'm about to
crash out, bro.
>> Yo, say my name again, bro. You're going
to die.
>> Listen. Listen, brother. But you fell
before your shoes in the Nine and a
half.
>> Listen.
>> Yo, don't get anywhere near me, bro.
>> Listen. Listen.
>> But you filled before, right? That I
wanted you to throw in the pool.
>> Yes.
>> But how you forgot about that?
>> It's okay. I'm doing for you for content
making money.
>> Okay. I'll let you like a low low kick.
>> Okay. You're going to check my kick.
>> No. No.
>> All right. We're even. All right.
Oh, no. You're sweaty. Okay.
>> Sweaty, brother. You just pushed me in
the pool. My
>> phone's gone.
>> My phone's right here, bro.
>> Can you give me a change of clothes?
>> Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
>> For sure.
>> Ambassador Louis,
>> I need underwear. Can I have your
underwear,
>> brother?
>> It's going to fit me.
>> Different size, you know.
>> It's okay. It's okay.
>> You have your mic?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> At least your hair didn't get wet. Yeah,
>> you got the hair still.
>> Yeah, you see your hair is good.
>> You know I can't swim.
>> It wasn't even It wasn't.
>> No, that's what I'm saying. But if it
was, I would have died.
>> It was a lifeguard,
>> huh?
>> I'm a lifeguard.
>> I know.
>> CPR everything. I know all of it.
>> I appreciate you, Nina. You're the only
You know what?
>> It's okay. I got you.
>> Face off of me.
>> Yeah, that's good.
>> No, no hands. No hands.
>> Do you want Do you Do you want this?
>> No, no, no, no, no, brother.
>> I'm tired of hearing your voice. I'm
tired. I'm sick of your [__] Right.
Mia, hold the cash, please.
>> No, no, don't do that. Don't do that.
Well,
>> now everything's out.
>> Hold the cash.
>> Finally, someone washed your clothes,
you know.
>> I'm sorry. I
>> You smell [__] But now I washed you.
>> You washed me.
>> Yeah. Like
>> what am I a [__] dog,
>> bro? But you smell [__] Like when I was
sitting, even you felt that smelling
yourself. How it's possible? So we I see
you only wearing these sneakers. So take
him to Kali,
change sneakers.
So we washed it. Tomorrow is going to be
dry. You're going to wear in uh Vegas
and be good.
>> Okay.
>> But what?
>> It's a good clip.
>> This uh this side was was like a no
deep. That's why I throw I threw you
here.
>> You're such a nice guy, brother.
>> You're such a nice guy.
>> Next time I throw in the deep
>> and I'll save you.
>> Okay, let's do the video. Okay, cut it
down.
>> HOW THE [__] AM I going to do the video?
>> It's okay, brother. Who gives a
>> Who gives a wet?
>> Wait, this is the part where you
>> The doesn't even fit anymore. Like, why
is he wet? You know, in the video.
>> It's okay. It's okay.
>> This is the part where you have to hang
on my leg.
>> Do you have the new clothes that I gave
you?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Here.
>> No, I don't.
>> Oh, what the A? Thanks, bro.
>> So sweet.
>> Everything. Whatever you want.
>> Thanks.
>> I'm going to go change. I'll be back.
>> This looks planned.
>> Okay, say bye. Say bye to to Chad. We
going to do idiot. here.
>> I have to end my stream.
>> No, you don't want
>> Uh, no. Let me change and I'll end. They
come and change with me. Actually, no.
Leave it there. I'll be back.
>> There's a bathroom here.
>> Bathroom there. All right.
>> Oh, 12 ft.
>> How long will the video take?
>> Oh my god. He just pushed Nina.
>> Oh my god.
What are we supposed to do as a [__]
UFC fighter? YOU'RE A BULLY. YOU'RE A
[__] bully, dog.
>> Nina, are you okay? I'mma save you. Oh
no, it's deep. I can't. Is your phone in
your pockets?
>> Oh my. Take it out.
>> Oh my god.
>> My money.
>> Your money?
>> Yeah.
>> Um
and my shoes
>> and my hair.
>> Why you looking at me? Look at him like
that.
>> But who IS THIS?
>> THAT'S MINE, YOU PIECE OF [__]
>> WHY YOU THROW your thing here?
>> That's That's what they put in my shoes.
Glad they wouldn't crease. Oh no,
they're your shoes.
>> Oh no.
>> Just throw them in the trash can. It's
over. Yo, brother. Yo, brother. I'm
going to get you back so bad. I'm going
to get you back so bad, bro. Watch.
Watch. Nice war. Real [__]
>> Oh no.
>> I'm going to get you back so [__]
bad, bro.
>> How's water? How's water, brother? You
want to see? You want to see how the
water is?
>> You think you're going to throw me in
the water, brother? Your whole team and
bodyguard cannot do that.
>> This is so
>> I'm going to change, bro.
>> What do I change?
>> Nina, you know what? I'm going to be
honest. We got [__]
>> Yeah. Lost money and [__]
>> I'll do anything.
>> Neil, you should jump.
>> Oh, bro. No. I'm not going that way.
Where? Where else can I Oh, thank you.
All right,
>> Mia, can you give the um cuz her cash
got [__] can you give the cash back
to her?
>> I got I got a jacket, right?
>> All right. Uh Nina, just because you got
[__] over to, I'm sending the cash
back.
>> Look at this guy, bro.
>> He's a lunatic. He's a [__] Armenian
lunatic. No, don't move.
>> You're a lunatic, bro.
Yeah, finally someone bought this.
>> Wow. I never thought you I never thought
you you know I never thought you
>> No, it's got to be fair, you know. Not
only you would do that to me.
>> No, you found it.
That's why they saying that's why they
saying don't trust anybody in this life,
you know.
>> Let's make a video.
>> Oh, no. Right.
>> Oh,
>> no. Like this. You look You look way
better.
>> You okay, Nina?
>> This is not
>> No.
>> Is it back in?
>> I end up in a worse position than you.
>> Okay, let's do it. We got to We got to
We got to Oh, you know it's my brand.
>> This is your band. This is my friend.
I have say
>> cool. I'm blocking it.
>> But it's a it's a
>> I'm not I'm not shooting anything.
>> You ready for the video? I have to keep
streaming. So, I'll have him take over.
How long will the video take?
>> I'm not doing a video.
>> No. No. We got TO DO IT.
>> WHY would you push me before the video?
>> I bought all these things.
>> I don't Look at me.
>> I got you new clothes now. My hair, my
freaking hair, my makeup, everything.
>> Hold on. Should I push her?
>> Should I push her?
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> So, we're not doing it.
>> No. No. We got to do it,
>> brother. She
good, bro. Back up.
>> Let's go. Let's go. Let me get you the
clothes.
I'm getting prices for tomorrow, Arman.
Huh?
>> I'm getting prices for tomorrow.
>> You got the contract.
>> The what?
>> You got your contract?
>> What contract?
>> Oh, you see what he got?
>> You have something more in the car.
>> Wait, where's my jacket? Mia, you have
my jacket.
>> But it's all wet.
>> Is my jacket wet, too?
>> Are you sure?
>> Where we going? One second.
>> I don't know where we're going, bro.
>> Wait, I want to see your gym.
>> I think I think the phone's on the
counter,
>> bro. Chad, what the [__] was that?
>> What do we do?
>> I don't know. Do you still want to do
this video? Are you okay? Come here.
Bring it. What do we bring? How do we
stop him?
>> I don't know. He's like a maniac. He
showed up.
>> He's a [__] psychopath.
>> He [__] took all this money. He took
all my money and pushed us in his pool.
And now
>> I want to get him. I want to get him
back tomorrow.
>> I'm just standing here. My mics are
dead. They're all wet,
my shoes,
my hair,
everything.
>> Good.
>> Well, at least he walks around like he
don't give a [__]
>> I know.
>> He don't give a [__]
>> Look at him. He's on the phone now.
>> He don't care.
>> [__] [__]
>> Hey, brother. Love you.
>> Who's talking to right now? You know.
>> Love you, bro.
>> What phone call is he on? What phone
call is he on?
>> Why you looking at her toes?
>> What happened with your toes?
>> Oh, no. It's like uh from the socks. I
have good feet, bro. Look, love good
toes. Hold on.
>> Um, okay.
>> I get my toes done, brother.
>> Can I see your gym?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> The You have the jacket or is it wet?
>> Yeah, it's wet.
>> [__] me. Um, do you have a hoodie of
your brand, bro?
>> Yeah. You cold?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm cold.
>> No. No. It's okay.
But it's okay.
>> Nah's leaving.
>> Huh?
>> Nina's leaving.
>> No. No. No. No home. No home. We got to
make a video.
>> No. No. I can't make a video. I don't
have any clothes.
>> We're going to get you clothes. Don't
worry.
>> Just do it like this.
>> Yeah.
>> No, the two of you stopped saying that.
>> Oh [__]
>> I think she's mad. No, she's
>> okay. She's good.
>> It's your fault.
>> You want
>> Yeah. So, um I need you from you my
video and then you can get out of here
>> and we meet tomorrow.
>> Yeah. 1 or 12 p.m.
>> Get the jet.
>> Splitting it.
>> Yeah, split it. But you get the jet or
I'll get the jet.
>> Split it.
>> Split it three ways. Okay. I'll get the
I'll just I'll pay for it and we can get
the money later.
>> Yeah, we'll figure out in the Vegas.
>> You [__] I'm getting the money
before I go. By any chance you have a
hoodie, brother?
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
You're a piece of [__]
>> Hey. Hey. Come on. Come on.
Yeah.
>> Where's the bathroom?
>> Go straight and make a right.
>> You have these like things ready for the
people the the the clothes you give them
after you push them in the pool.
>> No.
>> Your your friend pushed us in the pool.
>> Uh can you give your uh the hood to
>> No problem.
>> Yeah. Take it.
>> Oh, he's he's bringing me one.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Take it. And then we we give
>> No, no. Where this one? Where?
>> Which one's better? You give the Nina
this one. You don't want to uh do the
name for me
>> because you don't want to advertise my
brand.
>> No, I want to advertise your brand.
>> So you
>> I hit it for a minute, bro, and then put
it back. I'm a real friend, bro.
>> Thanks. All right. Show change and we'll
do the video. Yeah.
>> Let me see a gym real quick.
>> He's not ready yet.
>> But we can show you the
I'll show you, bro. When you come to my
house, I'll show a place where I built
special for my for my guest like you.
Like a place where you can stay.
>> Oh, like a guest house.
>> [__] How am I going to
>> Yo, brother. Are you [__] kidding me?
Oh, really? Really?
>> What the [__] is this,
bro? It's not even stable.
Hold on, JCB.
>> So, we prepared for you, you know.
>> Is that a treehouse?
>> Yeah.
So, we put that the store here,
everything for you. Set it up. It's a
guest house.
>> I'll be there soon, bro.
>> [__] hell. This guy, bro. This
[__] guy.
>> Just give her like a couple here. I'll
open that. It's going to be a jig.
>> Yeah.
>> When did you get this place?
>> Good talk, brother.
>> Here is going to be
>> Oh [__]
>> You see the future here?
>> I see it. Oh. Oh.
>> Don't touch it.
>> Can I have it?
>> This one? Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Wait, no. I already have your gloves. I
have the gloves. You
>> mean the gloves?
>> I have the gloves. It's hanging up in my
my room or my house.
>> You just put this on?
>> Yeah.
>> Tuna.
>> Try. What is he saying? I just want to
show one thing, but I'm thinking it's
good or not. Let's Let's turn that way.
Cameras.
>> Car. No, no, that way. Don't show. Don't
show. I just show to him.
>> No. No. That way. That way.
>> Just keep it on me.
>> Yeah.
>> No. Just
one.
>> Go.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right. Yeah. All
right, brother. What the [__] is that?
>> Just
>> How you doing, brother? Brother,
>> you want to see?
>> No, I don't want to see.
>> I don't want to see. I don't want to.
Hey,
>> you good?
>> Yeah,
>> bro. That is crazy.
He just showed me the craziest [__]
Okay. All right. Ready for the video?
>> Let's do it.
>> All right.
>> You're so hot,
>> brother. By any chance, they're socks.
>> Socks?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I feel homeless.
>> I didn't bring it to you.
>> You are homeless.
>> Yo, bro.
Are you [__] kidding me, bro?
>> I know how much you mean. So much.
>> Chill. Chill. Chill. Chill.
>> So, tomorrow jet on you, bro.
>> No. Come on. Split, bro. Split.
>> Listen. Clips on me tomorrow.
>> You pay for the clips?
>> Yeah.
>> The clips are going to cost more than
the jet.
>> No, no, no. Clips on me.
>> You get the clips.
>> Yeah. People going to do clips anywhere,
you know.
>> Yeah. when I'm going to be there.
>> Okay.
>> So, clips
on me. You on your jet
>> on me. We're flying economy, brother.
>> No jet.
>> Economy. I had the the worst experience
in my life.
>> I saw the video.
>> I don't want to fly economy ever.
>> At least uh JSX or or
>> Okay. Worst case, if the jet's too
expensive, JSX
>> clips.
>> I have no idea. He pays
>> expensive. The Indians. The Indians
post.
>> How much you pay per day?
>> How much clips?
I'll pay it.
>> You'll pay it?
>> Yeah. How much is that?
>> Like 20 40 20 30 40K depending on the
stream
>> for a stream.
>> It just depends on how good the stream
does. It's based off
>> It's based off performance.
>> No.
>> Thank you so much, brother.
>> No, I don't believe it.
>> No, you I'll show you.
>> $20,000 for clips.
>> Uh if it's a big stream, sometimes it's
like 510.
>> Don't lie.
>> I wouldn't lie, bro. You I have proof.
>> Who was the When was the biggest stream
for you?
>> Um I did a stream with an NBA guy, his
name is Jello. We paid out It was like
um 100K for a day.
They got like
>> Yeah. His m his song got like
>> Yeah. His song He got a record deal. He
signed a $10 million record deal because
of the stream.
>> He's a basketball player.
>> Yeah. Basketball. But now he's a rapper.
>> So he's no NBA player.
>> What about But what about for your song?
>> Uh my song's um
>> for the clips.
>> I'm going to thumb throw it away. You
think it's [__] right?
>> I mean,
>> but does he pay for the clips?
>> It's nice. I like you, brother. Really?
>> I [__] with you. What do you mean
really? Yeah, bro. He grew up. It's very
catchy.
>> It's catchy.
>> You want to [__] with an Indian?
>> Yes.
See?
>> Yeah, but it's like everybody going to
make make laugh at you.
>> No, they're not, bro. They like it.
They're Bro, they're making dances to
it, bro. They like it.
>> They dance to it.
>> At least try singing it once.
>> One more time.
>> She want to hang with an Indian. She
want to hang with an Indian. Imagine me
singing it. Madison Square Garden.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Do it. Do it. Go. Go. Go.
Go.
>> She want to hang with an Indian. She
want to hang with an Indian.
>> Who wants that?
>> What do you mean? Who wants that?
>> The girls.
>> What do you mean, which one?
>> Do it again.
>> You know what, Arman? sick.
>> Do the part. Do the the Iggy part where
you want to
>> Oh, I have to after I the lyrics I'm
still trying to memorize them.
>> You don't know the lyrics of your song?
>> I didn't write it.
>> Oh,
>> yeah.